

SHIVANGI GUPTA

SENIOR VIDEO EDITOR



Phone

+91 8182843659 +91 7379588695



F-mail

shivangigupta29113@gmail.com



PROFILE

I am Senior Video Editor at Design Pond Agency, Gurugram. Specialized in visually compelling videos for social media and advertisements. I also manage shoots and be core member of production team. I have mastered various applications and video edit techniques through clipping, illustration, animation, motion graphics, audio enhancement, grading, and exporting.



SKILLS



















EDUCATION









WORK LINKS

Showreel: https://youtu.be/W9hvo_Ptmms

Behance link: https://www.behance.net/shivangigupta27

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/shivangi-gupta-60067a22b



WORK EXPERIENCE



Design Pond Agency, Gurugram (Feb 2023-Present)

Working as Senior Video Editor at Design Pond Agency, I have worked extensively on editing IBS Hospital videos, showcasing expertise in enhancing visual narratives for the healthcare industry. I also manage shoots and assist the production team.



Design Pond Agency work playlist link



Mercer | Mettl, Gurugram (Dec 2021-Jan 2023)

Worked Junior Editor in core design team of marketing department, I edit and make it attractive videos for promoting Mercer | Mettl by generating new ideas for video. Been a part of core design team of marketing department. I made video based social posts on weekly basis. Explainer video with real footages. Edit client's testimonial videos. Event Promo videos. Platform Demo videos and special occasion festival videos. I also handled shoot based videos.



Mercer | Mettl work playlist link



City Focus Media, Varanasi (Aug 2021-Nov 2021)

Worked as Intern trainee at City Focus Media - Varanasi, to create static social posts and video composting for TVC and Ad commercials. Proficient in making static banners, posters and videos for social media advertisements.

City Focus Media work playlist link



Freelancer (2020-2021)

Worked as freelancer for various restaurant and retail shops for making logo, poster, menu card, certificate, photo editing and video editing for social media.

- Link 1 Nation with NaMo work
- Link 2 The Yellow Chilli menu card
- Link 3 Behance